{"data":[{"question":"While his racking days, racehorse John Henry earned a record 6.5 million, 2.3 million more than his closest competitor.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"While ","b":"earned ","c":"his ","d":"competitor","answer":"1","explain":"- While-> In","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Cartilage covers the ends of bones helps to protect the joints from wear and tear.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"covers ","b":"the ends ","c":"to protect ","d":"from ","answer":"1","explain":"- Covers-> covering","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The Alaskan malamute, used extensively to pull sleds, is closely reacted to the wolves.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"used ","b":"to pull ","c":"closely ","d":"wolves","answer":"4","explain":"- Wolves-> wolf","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Many of the characters portrayed by writer Joyce Carol Oats is mentally ill.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Many of ","b":"portrayed ","c":"is ","d":"ill","answer":"3","explain":"- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The new system responds at seconds to any emergency.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The ","b":"responds ","c":"at ","d":"any ","answer":"3","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The GATT is an international agreement designing to increase trade among member nations.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"international ","b":"designing ","c":"among ","d":"member nations","answer":"2","explain":"- Designing-> designed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The United States celebrate the birth of its independence every Fourth of July.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"celebrate ","b":"birth ","c":"its ","d":"every ","answer":"4","explain":"- Every-> on every","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Laminated safety glass is produced with combining alternate layers of flat glass and plastic.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"safety ","b":"with ","c":"alternate ","d":"flat ","answer":"4","explain":"- Flat->flatbed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"In one type of laminating, alternate layers of wood are placed with their grains running at night angles to each others.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"alternate ","b":"are placed with ","c":"running ","d":"each others","answer":"4","explain":"- Each others->each other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"In general, prawns live shallow coastal waters or in streams.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In general","b":"live shallow ","c":"waters ","d":"streams","answer":"2","explain":"- Live shallow-> live in shallow","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}